baklol.com 2018-12-09

# Privacy

## PRIVACY

**Updated on 23rd May 2018**  
At BakLOL, Privacy policy is taken with extreme care.We take user`s personal information seriously and we have made suitable measures to protect the privacy of our users. **

## Non-personally-identifying information

** Non-personally-identifying information is the information which we gather to maintain the integrity of BakLOL and to safeguard its TOS(Terms of services). This information includes time of browsing our website and number of requests made, language, browser information which helps in better understanding of its users to serve them better, this information is shared in an aggregate and statistically and is never specified to any third party website. Such information is collect to serve better ads to users and to consider the standard of BakLOL when sharing the progress of its online usage, We do collect Ip addresses to verify the country of users but its never shared with other websites, Its only used for internal quality purpose of BakLOL. Such Non-personally-identifying information is helps us maintain website standards and serve the needs of its users, Although this information does not identify a user but still its not shared with anyone, It helps making rough statistics website users and their interactions with BakLOL.  
**

## Personal-identifying information

** Personally-identifying information includes information such as Name, email, profile pic, age, gender etc. This info is used to verify users and members, this helps in making a connection between users and BakLOL, As the members are the core part of BakLOL community they help in building BakLOL to new levels and It is required to keep this information to verify them, login and submit pictures to BakLOL, This information is kept highly confidential and never shared, marketed in any circumstances. This information may be used to give statistics about the BakLOL community members but the exact information pertaining to users will never be given in any condition.  
**Information Collected by Us.**  
We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of the Service. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from users of the Service:   
**Information You Provide to Us.**  
We receive and store any information you enter on the Service or provide to us in any other way. For instance, we may collect information you provide to us if you register on the Service, respond to surveys, contact us through customer service or by other means, or participate in promotions that we may offer from time to time. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.  
**Automatic Information.**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Service. Google, and our authorized agents, automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on server logs, including your IP address, cookie information, the page you requested, device and software characteristics (such as type and operating system), location, activity on the Service, ad data, referral URLs, device identifiers or other unique identifiers such as advertising identifiers (e.g., "ad-ID" or "IDFA").  
This traffic data is used to help diagnose problems with servers, analyze trends and administer the Service.  
We may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.  
Many companies offer programs that help you to visit or use the Service anonymously. While we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.  
**E-mail Communications.**  
We are very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below.  
**

## Cookies

** Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in the Service are visited and by how many people. Our cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or your screen name or e-mail address.

**

## Ads

** Ads are displayed on BakLOL to users when they browse, this help in serving products to particular individual needs, The ads displaying companies may set cookies on user`s browser to recognize their behavior and to serve them with better targeted products and service, BakLOL is not responsible for any such cookie setting, If a user does not want to be served with ads and their cookies they may clear their cookies and caches from time to time. BakLOL cannot be held responsible to ads clicked by a user and the content which was served, Users are advised to contact/report the concerned ad network about any such third party websites with inappropriate content. 

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings]().

Third-party vendors and ad networks can serve ads on our website. visitors may opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info. 

**

## Change of Privacy Policy

** BakLOL in its own discretion can change these privacy policies anytime, A notification may be sent to its members and contributors registered at that time, general non registered visitors are advised to check these privacy policies and changes before using the website. **

## Contact

** If you have any problem concerning with content, ads, privacy policy, TOS please feel free to contact us through our [contact form]().
